# **Kevin Choi**

#### **SCRUM Master**

SCRUM Master with 9+ years of managerial leadership and product management experience. I write well designed, testable, efficient code using the best practices of the latest web development platforms. I bring excellent customer service skills, strong problem solving skills and various leadership experience.



### **Personal Info**

## Address

Miami, FL 33137

#### **Phone**

(213) 321-1879

#### E-mail

kevinyoungchoi@gmail.com

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/choik305

#### LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevinch oi305/



### **Certificates**

#### 2019-04

SCRUM Master (PSM I)



### **Software**

Javascript	
Back-End Web Development	••••
React	
HTML	
CSS	
Ruby	
Ruby on Rails	
Git/Github	
Visual Studio Code	••••



### **Education**

#### 2017

#### **Wyncode Academy**

Full Stack Developer

#### 2008

### **University of Nevada, Las**

#### **Vegas**

Bachelor of Science in Hospitality Management



### **Projects**

#### 2018-02

#### Game of Thrones Web Application

Web App to create user knowledge of past seasons of Game of Thrones

- Designed a Web App using Javascript that interacted with the web browsers.
- Utilized React as a library to put all components together.
- Implemented HTML and CSS which enhanced visual and graphic user interface.
- Pulled API database from an Wiki page exclusively for Game of Thrones.



### **Experience**

**Wyncode Academy** - Received training in programming languages (JavaScript, Ruby, HTML/CSS), web frameworks and libraries(Ruby on Rails, Bootstrap, MVC, React), version control and database management (SQL, PostgreSQL, Git), as well as project management and development (GitHub, Agile Methodologies) Completed 350+ hours of staffed learning and 3,000+ lines of code Collaborated to build complex applications and original websites



## **Work Experience**

#### **Development Intern**

2019-04

2019-03 -

Miami Dev Shop

 Assisted with facilitating software, information technology, cloud services, software integration, consulting and developing websites.

#### 2009 -2018

#### **Owner Implementation Manager**

Easy Wear Inc

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Built and designed company website that catered to customer's demand.
- Uploaded newly added inventory to E-Commerce Platforms & Marketplaces.
- Facilitated the recruiting, interviewing, and hiring of new trainees.
- Monitored listings both front end and back end to enhance product description and visibility.
- Oversaw all departments and quality assurance.

#### 2008-04 -2009-07

### **Manager in Training**

Four Seasons Hotel and Resort

- Directed staff to assure guest rooms are cleaned to exacting standards.
- Anticipated guest needs, responded promptly to guest concerns and requests.
- Managed to main a cooperative, professional working style with supervisors and workers.
- Met strict deadlines and maintained quality control.